Hello!
What a surprise!
I'm here at the Tokkimeku Koibito Seishun Collaboration Cafe!
Yay!
Thank you!
It's Animax Cafe!
Yay!
We're so happy!
I think you could see us from outside.
Yes, you did!
From the first.
That's right.
I'd like to go inside right away.
Yes!
Let's see!
Oh, my God!
I haven't even looked at it for a long time.
Ours.
Oh, yeah.
Eh, it's cute.
Oh, there it is!
Cute.
From the outside.
It's nice from the outside.
Which one's the real one, Hitomi?
This one's the real one, right?
There's three of them.
Hito-chan, there are three of us.
I'm the real one.
You're so cute.
You're cute.
That's great!
Lots of vestries and stuff.
Congratulations!
Here you can see a lot of photos from the show.
This one is of a live performance from the very first album that I heard so much about.
I liked it too.
I'm sure.
It's always been good.
It's good to hate it.
Congratulations, Missa.
So you won't be lonely if you come alone, right?
Our members will eat with you.
You are welcome to come alone.
You are very welcome.
We are waiting for you.
There are shots of all of us.
We have a lot of them on various pillars.
There are a lot of them.
I have a lot of good pictures.
I was 1kg at the time, right?
I see.
Fun.
There are a lot of mestries.
Amazing.
Youth costumes, super.
Cute.
There is Rossmai.
Take lots of pictures here.
Take pictures.
You can see this story from outside,
I realized that it is a normal cafe.
You see for the first time?
It's a café.
Nice. Pose like you like it.
Sure.
Same pose.
I don't know.
And over here, love.
There's a panel of love.
A panel of fasion.
Cute.
This one is the mestlabry, guys.
The space here is so neat, take a picture.
It's cute.
This is amazing.
This is great.
I'm going to take a picture like this.
It looks good.
Oh, what do you see from here?
Ta-da!
Live video.
Music videos and various other things will be played.
Now it's a live video of the big day,
But there were a lot of music videos playing just now.
Yes, they are.
While eating and drinking.
Oh, it stopped.
Oh, it moved.
Sometimes there were people like this.
That's nice. Eating while listening to us sing.
When you see it, you keep looking at this and forget to eat.
Oh, it's cold.
Even though it's uncomfortable to sleep.
Yes, it is.
Be careful with that.
This is a life-size panel.
Well then. It's big.
Everyone, please take two shots with this Kanamine.
Oh, and over there?
Oh, that? Julia?
The real Julia?
Ta-da!
There is also a panel of Julia.
Is this Julia?
Or this one?
No cheeks and buttocks.
Both of them have ribbons on their heads.
Also today.
Kanamin gave me this ribbon.
It's cute.
Thank you.
It's so cute.
Everyone, please take a photo with Julia.
She's cute.
And next to her?
Don.
Wow.
Oh, oh, oh.
Something's not here.
Whoa. Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Talk a little more.
Yes, this is Soo-chan.
Earlier, you said you didn't know which one of us was more interesting, but I'm pretty sure that's a lie.
Seriously, I didn't recognize you for a moment.
Seriously, I couldn't tell at a glance. It's a lie.
I didn't recognize him because his face was so fixed.
We are about the same height.
I'm taller than her because she has heels.
Same height.
And next to her is Ai-chan.
Yes, yes.
She is positioned like an elevator girl.
Cute.
Person.
Oh, your anime story is about the same.
Really? And since you've been on a roll lately.
You don't have any cartoons, do you? No. This one's doing well.
I think it'd be good to shoot something like this.
It's good.
That's great. Thank you.
It's not helping, is it?
That's great.
What do you call them? Oh, it's a sprout. Yeah, that's right.
I'd like to sign it or something.
Sure.
If you take a picture of it with the Maasai.
Yeah, I'll do that.
Elevator girl.
Look at that.
That's my big epanol in the shirt.
Now I'm wearing 12cm thick clothes, so I'm taller than 10 years old, but I think it's probably around the same.
But when I get up close, I can really see the details.
It's embarrassing to get so close, but if you want, you can take a picture with me.
Do it like this.
Aki-chan, please take a picture.
You can hug me.
Oh, maybe not.
And then, my neighbor.
Oh!
Something is real.
Hiyori!
Well, then....
I'm right next to this, uh, image.
When you are eating, you may be wondering whether you are watching this video or Hiyori Kamel's video,
Please watch them both.
And if you would like, please take pictures of them and give them a good kiss.
Please take pictures at everyone's place.
And here is the Lutz Combo!
He's so cute.
This alter ego is so thick.
So stylish!
So cute!
The color is cute too!
Try it on the model.
Can I wear it?
It's so cute!
It looks good on you.
It's so cute.
I want all of these plates.
The way the brim spreads out.
It's so cute.
Isn't it perfect for this season?
It's so cute!
So cute!
It's cute.
It's adorable.
And this one?
Very cute.
Oh, my God.
Is it random?
It's fun.
I'll ask around.
This is it.
Do you know who this is?
It's the moment of destiny.
It's fun.
What? What?
What's so great?
It's so cute.
I heard a sound.
I echoed it.
The color key of love.
Congratulations.
This one goes cold.
Magnet
Stick it on the fridge
Room style keychain
Name match also random.
Random.
Who wants to open it?
I'll open it.
Open.
Name match.
Let's see who comes out.
Let's see who's going to be there.
I'll have to write "Aki.
I see a little bit.
Oh no...
Oh, no!
Oh, my God.
It's a flick.
I can put it on.
I can put it on a bag or something.
It's so cute.
Look at that.
It's cute.
Case acrylic stick.
So cute.
That's a lot of goodies.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
These aren't random.
You can choose which ones you want.
You can specify.
Even sports.
What do you put in this?
Lips and stuff. Military.
They do candy and stuff like that.
I'm thinking like Greta Greta from Rumble Gumdrops.
That's cute.
I want one of these.
It's so cute.
It looks like you could put all kinds of stuff in it.
I want to put in a lot of milliture.
Oh, my gosh.
It's all open.
There's a name on it.
Hiyori Yoshikawa
You can wash it if it gets dirty.
Expedition-worthy.
It's so cute!
Cute
Room-style key chain
Room style key chain
It has a birthday written on it.
So cute!
Clear cute
Gradation
Stylish, isn't it?
This, this, this.
RON PILLAR
Same here.
Cute with boss
Use it for sleeves
stylish
6 pieces
Stylish.
What size is this?
L.
You can wear it like a dress.
It's cute.
That's all.
Check it out!
Enjoy!
Now let me introduce you to the cafe menu!
Bon appétit!
Lots of menu.
Cute.
There are food items, deja vu items, and drinks.
We thought of it ourselves, didn't we?
And what's this?
This is cute.
We also drew pictures.
We drew a picture of fireworks.
We drew a lot of pictures and chose one of the miraculous portraits.
I was addicted to drawing portraits.
They appear in various places. Here is a recent portrait of me.
It looks like you can get a drink as soon as possible, so let's have it.
Let's all close our eyes.
Please do.
Okay, I'll open in three, two, one.
Yes, sir.
Ready.
Three, two, one.
Wow!
It's beautiful.
Wow! Cute.
Smile.
This is so cute.
It's so cute.
It's so warm.
I definitely want strawberry milk.
It's so cute.
There's pineapple in it.
It's amazing.
Amazing.
It's true. It's warm.
Yes, even for candy.
It's warm.
It has pineapple.
When it's Autumn's, it's refreshing.
If you're cold, drink Autumn's.
When you order a drink, you get a coaster from last week.
Then, winter and dessert will come.
After drinking quickly, you get a coaster.
This one also has a cute service on it.
Straw tag.
Ehhh.
Cute.
This is cute, too.
Straw tag.
Two kinds of flowers.
Amazing.
This is also random.
I wonder which one will appear.
Looks delicious. Add some powdered green tea.
Can I drink this?
I want to drink it.
I do.
Then I'll drink it.
Cheers.
I'm going to fill it up.
Oh, there's cherry blossoms on it.
It's so delicious.
It's delicious.
Lychee soda.
It's so good.
It's delicious.
Snapple.
I drank a lot of pulp.
It's a little bit sticky.
What?
Isn't it amazing?
It's delicious.
I'm going to gobble it up.
Yes, it's good.
It's great.
It's rich.
It's thick.
The name wins.
Delicious.
Tasty lemon squash.
It's amazing.
I definitely like it with pulp.
Pulpy strawberry milk.
That's fancy, isn't it?
It's delicious.
Campetti.
You're a fashionable guy, aren't you?
I wish you could eat it, too.
I did.
Dessert.
Did everyone eat?
What's this?
Canamine cocoa?
Everything is canamine.
I actually looked at it.
The illustration I thought.
Illustration I drew.
It's fluffy.
It's cute.
The skin is cute.
Cute.
It was worth the dozens of minutes of work.
There was only one left.
What a waste of time to drink it.
It was worth it.
That too.
What is this? It's cocoa.
It's cute. A mustache.
With a mustache.
Cocoa.
This is cocoa.
What's "with whiskers"?
There are cafe au lait and cocoa.
Everyone orders this type of drink and food or dessert first,
The last one.
Hot drink.
Cafe au lait.
What about you, Azi?
What about you?
Hot from hot.
Certainly.
Cocoa from here.
Let's have cocoa from here.
So, shall we have some rub too?
Yay.
Yay!
Yes, please.
What do you want?
Can you do it?
With peanuts.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Oh, me too.
Me too.
Oh, here it comes.
In Rome?
Here it comes.
Five seconds?
Five seconds.
Five seconds, everybody's hidden.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Open.
You look so pretty.
Makeup.
Okay.
Stylish.
It's so big!
Very, very, very cute.
You guys are huge!
It's huge!
What's this?
It's funny.
Oh, my God.
It's so stylish!
It's so cute!
Very stylish prints!
Cute.
It's adorable.
Am I the only one who made a mistake?
Yes, I did.
That's...
I'm the only one with a large serving.
I'll show you.
I filled it with the fruit of the month.
Fruit sandwiches!
You've done a lot of things your own way, haven't you?
It's a bit sparse.
I thought you didn't like bananas.
You like bananas?
I heard a lot of voices when I asked her, but yes, she doesn't like bananas.
But everyone likes bananas. Yes, yes, yes, I like bananas.
So I wanted to include what everyone likes, not just what I like, so yes, bananas are included.
So, it looks delicious!
Next up for me is the melt-in-your-mouth fondant chocolat of my crush's love.
I'm so happy because I love fondant chocolates so much. I'm so happy.
Next is my hearty omelet hamburger steak. Looks delicious.
Yes, it's a solid and hearty rice dish. Cute.
So cute. The heart-shaped egg is cute. Cute.
Yes, I am Oharu's particular ramen and fried rice set.
This way. You can eat a lot.
Isn't this amazing? This. Isn't this amazing? This.
If you're here for dinner, please come out.
Hey, it's big. It's great.
Next, I'm going to make fluffy cotton candy pancakes. It's so cute!
It's amazing. It's pretty fluffy. Wow.
Pancakes. You should try them.
Is this honey? I like it. I like honey.
Honey.
I'd like to try it.
Oh, that's nice.
Will it melt?
It's glowing.
Oh! Melted?
It's melted.
Maybe it's melting.
Wow, it's so beautiful. It's like art. It's cute. It's cute. It's cute. It looks like it would look good on Instagram.
It's amazing. It's done. It's nice. It's cute.
It's got lemon on it, too.
And Hiyori's handmade pulled peas.
Eggs, eggs.
Indeed, the dough is absolutely crispy, and the vegetables on top are so much fun to look at.
Girls and boys, please try it.
I want to eat it.
I want to eat all of them.
Cheese.
Looks delicious.
Bon appétit.
It's Kurechi-san. Bon appétit.
Which one shall I eat?
Mine.
Which one?
You want to try?
Well, I love oranges.
Always oranges.
Oranges.
Bon appétit.
Delicious.
It's amazing.
Looks delicious.
Bon appétit.
It's full.
It's full. It's amazing.
It's filled to the brim.
It's amazing.
It's delicious.
There's a lot of food in here.
It's so good. And the oranges are fresh and not too sweet, which makes the fruit inside stand out.
Delicious.
Good luck with the bread.
Hey.
Cream again.
Now then, Julia, the global warming bag.
Let's cut it first.
It's so thick.
Mellow.
It's yammy.
This is the best, isn't it?
This is amazing. It's so good.
It's cute.
I quit.
It's so cute.
Self.
It's so rich.
Very thick.
I love it.
It's absolutely delicious.
It's great. I'll have some ice cream too.
I like it. It's refreshing.
It's so good.
Looks delicious.
Yeah, it is.
The ice cream is great, too.
The chocolate is super rich.
It's both rich and refreshing.
It was rich and herbaceous.
It's good.
Chocolate, it turned black.
Super delicious.
Bye bye. Next is Hiki-chan.
Looks delicious.
Oh, I see...that's right... This.
Should I have done this with my hands?
Go, go, go.
Oh, parity corn.
Oh, put it in here.
Parity corn?
He's most pleased.
Satan Sir.
Amy, you finally did it.
Oh!
That's good. That's good.
I'm going to do it like this.
كل 79%
I like this feeling.
People who didn't get to eat it because of some kind of punishment.
Amazing!
So cute!
And this demi-glace sauce!
The whole thing is so well balanced!
Delicious!
Hamburger steak
Good hamburger steak!
Delicious!
Yummy.
Cute.
Mm.
Mmm!
Delicious.
It's so meaty.
It's amazing.
It's delicious.
It goes well with it.
Looks delicious.
Delicious.
Go for it!
Bon appétit!
Is this the pink one from Bujiro?
Bujiro's cute!
Bujiro is cute!
The point!
A lot of Bujiro
Bon appétit!
Yum! Delicious!
Delicious!
I'm trying my best.
Mmmm.
Delicious!
Looks delicious. I'm getting hungry.
It's so hearty. It's delicious. It's delicious.
Wow. There's also fried rice.
There's also fried rice. It's great.
I'll have fried rice too.
I'll have the fried rice.
I'm getting hungry.
Yum! Delicious! It's so easy to eat.
Yum! Delicious. Not at all.
I think I can eat it easily. I think I'm going to eat it at a dinner party.
There are wontons in it, so there are lots of ingredients. It's delicious.
After your meal, you should definitely try the sweets. Yes, it's a pancake.
Pancakes. I love fluffy pancakes. They're amazing.
Nice. It's cute. Hey, it's cute. So many.
Mmm.
Fluffy.
Delicious!
I think everyone will probably finish it in an instant.
Yeah, I'll have to ask Misako.
I might have to ask Misako.
It's very solid.
That's why it's so good.
It's kind of stuffy.
But it's so fluffy and delicious.
Try it.
Look at this.
It looks like cat ears.
Scary, isn't it?
Meow!
So cute!
Don! I'll cut it out.
Hey, I'm going to put this ASMR thing in!
ahaha!
This is the type of thing I was looking for.
Thick and solid.
Ta-da!
It's delicious!
I eat a lot of luttia salad.
You eat it together a lot.
Yes, we do.
You're a debutante, right?
Root Appeal.
You've entered the field, right?
How often do you eat together?
We really, really eat our vegetables together with our rutillas.
That's right.
It kind of dries you out.
Bon appétit.
Mmm.
Yum.
Yum! Pounding!
It's like cheese powder.
Caesar.
Caesar!
Caesar salad.
You know what?
It's important to eat your vegetables first, right?
Yeah.
If we get a lot of publicity...
How about sharing one of these with everyone?
How about it?
Sure.
I'm picking up a few other things.
And you'll be happy.
It's a great meal time.
You could make it like coffee, couldn't you?
Salad.
Cosco.
A course of lasers
Dipped in chocolate
Hot.
Oh, really?
Yup.
It's good.
What?
What? I'm sorry.
I think I may have found a secret.
What? What?
What?
That's a rock-paper-scissors action.
What? If you put it down...
It's a count.
Oh! Ta-da!
Oh, yummy!
Here, the bottom one is chili meat flavored!
Oh, my gosh!
So, you know, I think I might be full on my own.
Oh!
Oh, my gosh!
There's some kind of meat in there!
Oh, my God!
I love it.
Oh!
Mmm-hmm.
It's so good!
A little spicy.
It's chili meat.
But you know what?
It's so good!
Oh, this is good.
It's good. It's good.
It smells so good. Both of them.
I want it all.
Delicious.
So, with so many delicious dishes on the menu, I hope you all come back and try as many as you can!
There's an order formu.
If you look at the menu and have a hard time deciding what you want, you can order 1 fruit sandwich if you want 1 fruit sandwich, for example.
For example, if you want a fruit sandwich with your favorite fruit, you can write "1" on it.
If you want to have it as dessert, you can choose to have it served afterwards.
You can also choose the timing of your order.
Please have them write it here.
Please write it down and hand it in.
Thank you!
And, what's more, you can get an original ranchmat for each visit!
You can get one when you come in.
You can also get one at random.
So you may be able to complete it after 3 visits.
Or you may never get it.
Yes...
She's so cute.
So cute!
To the mix of love and youth and love and youth
Sapira Blue
Sapira Blue.
You know what, keep this when you can use it for someone named Rancho Matto.
Maybe you can make it into some kind of poster like this.
Please make a complete set too!
Please do!
We're waiting for you!
We are waiting for you
Waiting for you
Yes, I painted it. Everyone, please take lots of pictures with this daddy.
I'm going to draw a fan.
It's done!
Take a picture!
I drew it!
In the season
OK
Thanks for watching!
I'm not sure why you're here.
Please check out this one too!
Something about the staff
Hey.
They're here.
Knock, knock!
Goo!
Ok.
Okay.
Yes, sir.
Oh!
Leave it as it is.
Yes, OK!
OK!
Ta-da!
It's done!
Yes!
I'm happy with the drums!
Satisfied!
Thank you!
I was everyone's companion!
Really, the drinks are good, the lettuce is good, and the food is good,
I think you will probably enjoy it no matter how many times you come,
Please try to complete all of them!
Please come and see us!
Come and visit us!
And souvenirs from everyone!
I got souvenirs from everyone!
Let's go home and take care of everyone!
Yes! I'm going home!
Thank you for the food!
Thank you for your hard work!
See you later!
See you later! Let's go home!
Thanks for dinner!
You can't do this!
This one!
No, no, no, no!
You can't do this!
I'm done!
Again!
No take-out!
No takeout,
Please leave it!
Well, maybe not!
Please take it home!
Cute, but no!
Leave me alone!
Bye-bye!
I'll put it back where I found it!
I'll put it back!
Oh, no!
Then it's real, it's real!
Well, they're taking you home!
Bye-bye!
Bye bye!
I don't know why, but when I laugh.
It's like the world is shining
I can turn my umbrella around and take it easy
Because otherwise I wouldn't be able to walk
I'm sure somewhere someone's crying
And somewhere I'll get my body wet again
I hope it's not too cold
I'm sure that somewhere someone is crying
Just a little bit of my feelings
I want to share it with you
I still don't know what's in front of me
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye, thank you for yesterday
After the rain, the cityscape turns color
And on the canvas of my broken heart, I paint a piece of the future
And it's guiding me on the way
I can say it now
Whenever you're lost, just remember the reason for your tears
And when it's raining, I'll smile
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny sky, making puddles of sound
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny day, I'll cover up my tears
I'll wear a rainbow dress
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
I'm gonna wear a rainbow dress
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
Chorus Is earn
Mai except
Please subscribe to our channel!